Features of the app:
1.	Each time the App Launches connect to a remote file, which contains sample JSON for some fictitious art galleries.
2.	Display a map, plotting a point for each of the locations found in the data. When a user selects one of the points, display some info for that gallery in the popup view.
3.	Allow the user to then select that gallery, taking them to the next screen. On loading the next screen, first check if there is a local storage entry (database or alternative) for this art gallery. If not, create one, including a record for each piece of art, based on the number listed in the data.
4.	The art gallery screen should display a scrollable view that contains an entry for each piece of art, so the user can scroll past each piece. 
5.	Allow the user to "rate" each piece of art.  This rating should also be stored locally, so that further views of this art gallery will display the original rating.
Additional 1.   Add an alternative "list" mode for displaying art galleries, instead of on the map.
Additional 2.   Add a splash screen that appears on the screen for 3 seconds after App launch.

This demo is not about imagery or visual design, however a demostration of code style and correctness.
